awprotools.com 2016-05-21

# AW Pro Tools - Privacy

**_Updated Oct 14, 2012_**

**PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE ACCESSING ANY AWProTools.comT OF THE WEBSITE.**

**I. OVERVIEW**

AWProTools.com Program, Inc. ("AWProTools.com," "us," "we," or "our") recognizes and respects the privacy of users of http://www.awprotools.com (the "Website").  The following privacy policy, as modified from time to time by us as described below (the "Policy"), tells you about the information that AWProTools.com collects through the Website and as a part of your use of the proprietary online customer communication and retention service offered through the Website (the "Service") and how we use the information we may collect.  If you access the Website and/or use the Service, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this Policy, as modified from time to time by us.

**II. UPDATES**

AWProTools.com reserves the right to make changes to this Policy at any time and will post any revised Policy on this page.  You will know we have changed the Policy when you see a new updated date at the top of this Policy.  We encourage you to check the date of this Policy whenever you visit this Website and/or use the Service so that you will know when you need to review the Policy for modifications.  Please note that this Policy applies to all information collected online by AWProTools.com whether through your use of the Website or your use of the Service.

**III. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION**

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact a person, including, but not limited to, a person's name, postal delivery address, e-mail address, user name, password, payment method (e.g., credit card or debit card) and telephone number, as well as other information when such information is combined with a person's personal information. When you register or use certain services available on our Website, we ask you to supply us with certain personal information (for both you and your customers) so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our services and marketing efforts.

For similar reasons, we may supplement the personal information you provide with publicly available information about you or your customers.  We use this personal information to process your registration, your payments, and to communicate with you on these and other topics, as well as to provide you more specialized and focused services through the Service.  We may also use your e-mail address to send you newsletters, promotional announcements, and consumer surveys.  Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us, including messages relating to your account transactions.

We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your Website activity, your historical Service data, payment history and correspondence, as well as any other related activity.  We use this information for such purposes as personalizing the Website to better reflect particular interests, tracking your level of activity, helping us quickly and efficiently respond to inquiries and requests and otherwise enhancing our Service for our customers.  We also provide analyses of our users in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties.  We may also disclose and otherwise use, on an anonymous basis, website habits, commentary, reviews, historical Service data and other non-personal information about customers and the Service.

**IV. VIEWING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION**

You are responsible for updating and maintaining the truth and accuracy of the personal information you provide to us relating to your account.  If you want to update your contact information, you should do so by visiting your user profile located on our Website.

**V. COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGY**

As you browse the Website, cookies may be placed on your computer's hard drive.  Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive for record keeping purposes.  In general, cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences on a particular site.  Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer.  If your browser is set to not accept cookies, you may not be able to use particular services on the Website or offerings through the Service.

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies, including pixel tags, to gather information on how our users interact with our Website and to otherwise help us efficiently operate and monitor our Website and Service.  These technologies show us, for example, popular pages, conversion rates, click-throughs and other information that can be used to improve, operate and monitor our Website and our Service.

**VI. DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We use other companies, agents or contractors to perform services on our behalf.  For example, we have partnered with other companies to personalize our web pages, process credit card transactions, collect debts, analyze and enhance data (including customers' interaction with our Website), and process consumer surveys.  In the course of providing such services, these other companies may have access to your personal information or the personal information of your customers.  These companies are not permitted to use such personal information except for the purpose of providing the services we request of them.

In addition, we often partner with third party companies, agents or contractors in order to offer joint promotions, advertisements, programs and marketing campaigns in which we believe our users (or their customers) may be interested.  These companies are not permitted to use your personal information  (or the personal information of your customers) except for the purpose of participating in the partnership arrangement for which AWProTools.com engages them.

AWProTools.com also reserves the right to disclose personal information when we reasonably believe disclosure is required by law, if we reasonably believe disclosure is necessary to establish or exercise legal rights, or in situations involving potential threats to physical safety.  In the event that AWProTools.com is acquired by or merged with a third party, we reserve the right to sell or otherwise transfer the personal information we have collected as part of that transaction provided that such third party continues to honor our privacy policy.

NOTWITHSTANDING ANYTHING SET FORTH HEREIN TO THE CONTRARY, AWProTools.com RESERVES THE RIGHT TO USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND THE PERSONAL INFORMATION OF YOUR CUSTOMERS (EXCLUSIVE OF ANY CREDIT CARD INFORMATION PROVIDED, IF ANY) FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE, IN AWProTools.com'S SOLE DISCRETION.  AWProTools.com may use your (or your customers') personal information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, text/short message services, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

**VII. SECURITY**

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account information and for restricting access to your computer or mobile device through which you access the Service. Users of public or shared computers or unprotected mobile devices should log out at the completion of each visit to our Website when you use the Service.

Unfortunately, no security system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  Accordingly, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and cannot assume liability for improper access to it.  By using the Service, or providing personal information to us through any means, you agree that we can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of this Website.

**VIII. CONTACT**

If you have questions concerning your account, please contact Customer Service.  If you have questions concerning this privacy policy, please email support@awprotools.com

Our address is 391 High Tide Dr., St. Augustine, FL, Attention: AWProTools.com Program Counsel.
